Hey, guys. Check it out!
嘿，伙计们。看看这个！
Science Bob just sent us tickets for his live show, Friday night.
科学鲍勃刚刚给我们寄来了星期五晚上他的现场表演的票。
I can't wait!
我等不及了！
Actually, you can wait. You just don't want to.
事实上，你可以等待。你只是不想等。
[sighs] It's a figure of speech, Ricky.
这只是个比喻，瑞奇。
- Ah, front row seats.
啊，前排座位。
We're Science B's VIPs.
我们是科学B的VIP。
I hope he does that experiment where he turns olive juice
我希望他做那个实验，用肌肉天文學把橄榄汁
into an olive, using muscular astronomy.
变成橄榄。
Actually, it's molecular gastronomy.
其实是分子美食学。
Which is the cooking or eating of fine food.
那是一种烹饪或享用精致美食的方式。
[all sighing]
[大家都叹气]
Whatever--as long as I get to eat that delicious olive.
无所谓——只要我能吃到那美味的橄榄就行。
Technically if it's made of juice,
严格来说，如果是用果汁做的，
you're drinking it.
你是在喝它。
[all sighing]
[大家都叹气]
Ricky, you don't have to be right all the time.
Ricky，你不必总是对的。
Yeah, you're always correcting us.
是啊，你总是纠正我们。
I don't always.
我并不是总是这样。
In fact, there's a lot of mistakes
事实上，你犯了很多错误，我觉得——
you make that I think-- "Eh, not worth it."
你犯的那些错误，我觉得——“呃，不值得计较。”
[doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
- Hey, Mae!
- 嘿，梅！
I got you a ticket for Science Bob's
我给你买了这周五科学鲍勃的演出门票。
show this Friday.
- 兴奋起来吧！ - 我很兴奋。
- Get excited! - I am excited.
但我不会去。
But I'm not going.
什么——为什么？
What-- why?
因为那是13号星期五。
That's Friday the 13th.
13号星期五也只是普通的一天
Friday the 13th is just a day
就像任何其他日子。
like any other day.
和其他日子一样。
You really don't believe in silly superstitions, do you?
你真的不相信那些愚蠢的迷信吧？
No, not silly ones. Just real ones.
不信，不愚蠢的那些。只相信真实的。
Like Friday the 13th-- It's bad luck.
比如星期五逢13日——会倒霉。
In reality, there's no such thing as bad luck.
实际上，并没有所谓的坏运气。
Friday the 13th is just a day like any other day.
星期五逢13日也只是和平常一样的日子。
- Don't correct my friend. - But you just said--
- 别纠正我的朋友。- 可是你刚刚说——
Pipe down, friend.
安静点，朋友。
You may know the answers to hard facts,
你可能知道硬事实的答案，
but you can't know for sure superstitions aren't real.
但你不能确定迷信不是真的。
Well, if you believe in superstitions,
嗯，如果你相信迷信，
aren't you worried about stepping on that crack?
你难道不担心踩到那个裂缝吗？
Step on a crack, break your mother's back.
踩到裂缝，会伤到你妈妈的背。
And see? Nothing happened.
看吧？什么都没发生。
[crash] [Anne] Ow, my back!
[撞击声] [安妮] 哎哟，我的背！
- Mom, are you okay? - She's fine.
- 妈妈，你还好吗？ - 她没事。
Yeah, I just tweaked my back carrying in
是啊，我只是搬进所有杂货时扭到了背。
all the groceries by myself.
对不起，亲爱的。
I'm sorry, hon.
我正准备在《杂货英雄》游戏中打破我的高分。
I was just about to beat my high score on Grocery Hero.
你拿起虚拟的杂货，把它们放在虚拟的货架上。
You take virtual groceries and put them away
你把虚拟的杂货放到
on virtual shelves.
虚拟的货架上。
Sleep tight, low-fat yogurt.
睡个好觉，低脂酸奶。
See, Ricky.
看吧，瑞奇。
Step on a crack, break your mother's back.
踩到裂缝，就会摔断妈妈的背。
Actually, Mom's back isn't broken.
实际上，妈妈的背没有摔断。
It just hurts.
只是受伤了。
Besides, this isn't bad luck.
而且，这并不是运气不好。
It's just bad Dad.
这只是爸爸不好。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇哇哇哇哇哇哇。
- He is not a bad dad. - I dropped the milk!
- 他不是个坏爸爸。 - 我把牛奶打翻了！
He is a bad husband.
他是个坏丈夫。
Noted.
记下了。
And I'll pick up the real groceries.
我会去买真正的杂货。
Excuse me, my atlas is getting cold.
不好意思，我的地图快凉了。
I am sick of Ricky being so sure he's right
我受够了瑞奇总是那么自信他是对的，
and always correcting us.
还总是纠正我们。
Yeah, and he does it to me all the time.
是啊，他老是这么对我。
Like he's more smartest than me.
好像他比我聪明多了似的。
We need to prove he can be wrong about something.
我们需要证明他也有可能出错。
What if we prove superstitions are real?
So you do think they're real?
[snorts] Of course not, they're ridiculous.
Sorry.
So in order to prove Ricky's wrong
about superstitions not being real,
we have to convince him superstitions are real?
Even though we know they're not real?
Yeah, exactly.
See, now who's more smartester?
[upbeat music]
♪ Na na na na na na ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na ♪ - ♪ One, two, one, two, three, four! ♪
♪ One, two, one, two, three, four! ♪
[upbeat music]
♪ Na na na na na na ♪
Okay, I loosened all the screws in Ricky's chair
好的，我已经松开了Ricky椅子上的所有螺丝
so when he sits down, it'll collapse
所以当他坐下时，椅子会因为他的“坏运气”而倒塌
because of his "bad luck" from walking under the ladder.
因为他走过了梯子下面。
And then he'll have to admit
然后他不得不承认
he was wrong about superstitions.
他对迷信的看法是错误的。
- Are you sure it's a good idea
你确定这样做是个好主意吗？
to be messing with superstitions like this?
这样玩弄迷信真的好吗？
What if Mae's right and--and there's something to it?
如果Mae是对的，而且——这里面真的有什么玄机呢？
I think it's a great idea.
我觉得这是个好主意。
It's clever, it's simple, and it's got the element of supplies.
这主意既聪明又简单，还带有物资的元素。
You mean surprise?
你是说惊喜？
No, supplies.
不，是物资。
We didn't have to buy any supplies.
我们不需要购买任何物资。
That's a good plan.
这是个好计划。
Sweetie, that's very nice of you,
亲爱的，你真是太好了，
but I told you, my back is fine.
但我告诉过你，我的背没事。
I can fold the laundry.
我可以叠衣服。
I know you can, I just feel bad
我知道你能行，我只是觉得不好
about not helping with the groceries.
没有帮忙买杂货。
Honey, I really appreciate it but it really--
亲爱的，我真的感激，但真的——
it's just better when I do this kind of stuff.
这种事情还是我来做比较好。
Oh, I see.
哦，我明白了。
It's because I don't do things the Anne Way.
是因为我没有按照安妮的方式做事。
Huh?
嗯？
Oh, you know what? You're right, Tom.
哦，你知道吗？你说得对，汤姆。
You know, I'm sorry, I should let you help out around here more.
你知道，我很抱歉，我应该让你在这里多帮忙的。
Ooh-- I was gonna do the floors next.
哦——我接下来打算拖地的。
- The floors? - Yeah.
- 地板吗？ - 是的。
Well, put me in, coach.
好吧，教练，让我上场。
I'm ready to sweep.
我准备好扫地了。
- Ohh. - [chuckles]
- 哦。 - [轻笑]
Move the chairs!
把椅子挪开！
I'm sorry. Do it the Tom Way.
对不起。按汤姆的方式来。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Real ma-chair, Anne.
真正的椅子大师，安妮。
I'm gonna put ma chairs back where ma want them.
我要把我的椅子放回我想要的地方。
Oh, Ricky? Lunch time!
哦，瑞奇？午餐时间！
You think I'm gonna be afraid to walk under a ladder?
你以为我会害怕从梯子下面走过吗？
I told you-- superstitions are bologna.
我告诉过你——迷信都是胡说八道。
Are you 100% sure?
你百分百确定吗？
Does this answer your question?
这个回答了你的问题吗？
What was his answer?
他的回答是什么？
What did you say?
你说了什么？
Dicky!
迪基！
What?
什么？
You walked under the ladder.
你从梯子下面走过去了。
I did?
我走过去了？
Twice!
两次！
And nothing happened,
而且什么事也没发生，
because there's no such thing as bad luck.
因为根本没有坏运气这回事。
We'll see about that.
我们走着瞧。
Hey, guys, what do you say we all sit down for some lunch?
嘿，伙计们，我们坐下来吃点午饭怎么样？
Sure.
当然。
Lunch always tastes better
午餐总是更美味
when you're sitting in a chair.
当你坐在椅子上时。
Go on-- sit, sit.
来吧——坐，坐。
[yells]
[大喊]
Dicky, are you okay?
迪基，你还好吗？
No, he's not okay.
不，他不好。
It's bad luck from walking under that stupid ladder!
都是因为走过了那个愚蠢的梯子带来的坏运气！
Oh, please, I walked under the ladder
哦，拜托，我走过梯子
and nothing happened to me.
而我什么事都没有。
How do you explain that?
你怎么解释这个？
I can't.
我解释不了。
But, I can't explain a lot of things,
但是，我解释不了很多事情，
like how do all the animals know where the zoo is?
比如所有的动物是怎么知道动物园在哪里的？
I saw this on Science Bob's website.
我在Science Bob的网站上看到的。
The vinegar curdles the milk.
醋使牛奶凝结。
Makes it chunky, sour, and gross.
让它变得块状、酸涩且恶心。
[all] Ugh.
[所有人] 呃。
All right, so phase two is set.
好的，第二阶段准备就绪。
Now for phase one.
现在进行第一阶段。
Nicky, where are the cream puffs?
尼基，奶油泡芙在哪里？
In the fridge.
在冰箱里。
Ahh, here they are.
啊，在这里。
Right above the fresh carton of milk.
就在新鲜牛奶盒的上面。
So, we gonna eat them while we discuss phase one?
那么，我们在讨论第一阶段时吃它们吗？
No, they are phase one.
不，它们就是第一阶段。
Why did phase two come before phase one?
为什么第二阶段会在第一阶段之前？
Did they change math again?
他们又改数学了吗？
No, math is the same.
不，数学还是一样的。
Phase one--Ricky eats the spicy cream puff.
第一阶段——Ricky吃辣泡芙。
What spicy cream puff?
什么辣泡芙？
This spicy cream puff.
这个辣泡芙。
Phase two--Ricky drinks the spoiled milk
第二阶段——Ricky喝变质的牛奶
to cool his mouth.
来冷却他的嘴巴。
Why would he drink spoiled milk?
他为什么要喝变质的牛奶？
'Cause he doesn't know it's spoiled.
因为他不知道它已经变质了。
Well then, who's gonna tell him?
那么，谁会告诉他呢？
Nobody!
没人！
We don't want him to know.
我们不想让他知道。
The whole plan revolves around the element
整个计划的关键在于
of not knowing.
他不知道这一点。
Oh, then I'm good.
哦，那我就放心了。
Now let's go get Ricky.
现在我们去把Ricky找来。
Ah, looks like Nicky's been baking.
啊，看来Nicky一直在烘焙。
And left a mess which, not to worry,
还留下了一片狼藉，不过别担心，
I will clean up.
我会清理的。
Oh. [chuckles]
哦。[轻笑]
But honey, I-- I thought you said
但是亲爱的，我——我以为你说过
you were gonna clean up.
你要清理的。
I will. In Tom time.
我会。在汤姆的时间。
But ah--there's milk out.
但是啊——牛奶在外面。
Noted.
知道了。
[stammers] But it's gonna spoil.
[结巴]但是它会变质的。
You know what, I'm so sorry. Sorry.
你知道吗，我很抱歉。对不起。
I will let you do it.
我会让你做的。
But I can't live in Tom time!
但我不能活在汤姆的时间线上！
Honey, I said I'd do it!
亲爱的，我说过我会做的！
[sighs]
（叹气）
Everything's gotta be done the Anne way.
每件事都得按安妮的方式来做。
Oh, boy.
哦，天哪。
Here, let me just--
来，让我——
There we go.
好了。
Good thing the floor is Tom clean.
好在地板是汤姆打扫干净的。
Well, it's not my hair.
嗯，这不是我的头发。
Ooh! Cream puffs!
哦！奶油泡芙！
My favorite!
我的最爱！
Mmm...
嗯...
Uh-oh.
哎呀。
Aaaah!
啊！
Fridge!
冰箱！
What the heck?
搞什么鬼？
Yuck. Looks like that milk is spoiled.
呸。看起来那牛奶已经坏了。
But this one's fresh as a daisy.
但这瓶新鲜得像朵雏菊。
Looks like it's my lucky day.
看起来今天是我的幸运日。
You said the good milk was in the fridge!
你说好牛奶在冰箱里！
It was!
确实是在！
Well, how do you explain this?
那你怎么解释这个？
- I can't! - And the cream puff switch?
- 我无法解释！- 还有奶油泡芙的调换？
- I can't! - And phase two happening
- 我无法解释！- 还有第二阶段在第一阶段之前发生？
before phase one?
好吧，那个我已经解释过了。
Okay, I already explained that.
剩下的我无法解释。
The rest I can't explain.
嗯，我能解释。这是梯子带来的坏运气！
Well, I can. It's bad luck from the ladder!
不，不是这样的。
No, it's not.
不，不是的。
Look, we just need to stick to the plan and convince Ricky superstitions are real.
听着，我们只需要坚持计划，让Ricky相信迷信是真的。
Look, I don't wanna tempt fate anymore.
听着，我不想再冒险了。
- I'm out. - No! Don't quit now!
我退出。不行！现在不能放弃！
Look, we're so close to proving Ricky wrong about something.
看，我们离证明Ricky在某件事上是错的很近了。
All we have to do is just come up with a plan
我们所要做的就是想出一个计划
that leaves nothing to chance.
确保万无一失。
Our Cousin Chance from Idaho?
我们爱达荷州的表弟Chance？
Why would we leave it to him?
我们为什么要依赖他？
He's a baby!
他还是个婴儿！
I saw him go in.
我看到他进去了。
Operation Broken Bathroom is a go.
‘破坏浴室行动’开始。
Oh, no!
哦，不！
Eew! Gross!
哎呀！好恶心！
Shoot!
该死！
Aaah!
啊！
Ohh-- aah!
哦——啊！
[breathing hard]
[呼吸急促]
What the--
这是什么——
There's no such thing as bad luck.
没有什么坏运气这回事。
There is such a thing as bad luck.
确实有坏运气这回事。
Help!
救命！
Let me outta here!
让我出去！
If the door handle's broken, how's he gonna get out?
如果门把手坏了，他怎么出去？
I took the hinge pins out of the door, so one good push will make it--
我把门上的铰链销子取出来了，所以用力一推就会——
[loud thud, thumping]
[巨大的撞击声，砰砰声]
Bad luck is real!
坏运气是真的！
I thought you don't believe in that sort of thing.
我以为你不相信这种事。
I didn't... but I walked under that ladder,
我没有...但我走过了那架梯子，
and now... all these things... one after another...
现在...所有这些事情...一个接一个...
it can't be a coincidence.
这不可能是巧合。
So you admit you were actually wrong about something?
所以你承认你实际上在某件事上是错的？
I... I guess I was.
我...我想我是。
Oh, my gosh.
哦，我的天。
Superstitions are real.
迷信是真的。
I heard you!
我听到了！
Superstitions are real!
迷信是真的！
Uh-oh.
哎呀。
Superstitions are real!
迷信是真的！
I think we broke Ricky.
我觉得我们把Ricky搞坏了。
Superstitions are real!
迷信是真的！
[cheerful whistling]
[愉快的口哨声]
Well, we got the door fixed.
好吧，我们把门修好了。
Superstitions are real.
迷信是真的。
Superstitions are real!
迷信是真的！
But Ricky's still broken.
但Ricky还是坏的。
Hey, buddy... you doing okay?
嘿，伙计...你还好吗？
I don't know. I don't know anything anymore!
我不知道。我什么都不确定了！
This is bad, Dawn.
这很糟糕，Dawn。
Don't worry. He'll bounce back.
别担心。他会恢复的。
You know, ever since he walked under that ladder,
你知道，自从他走过那个梯子下面之后，
strange, unexplainable things have been happening.
奇怪的、无法解释的事情一直在发生。
They're not unexplainable.
那些不是无法解释的。
They may not have gone as we planned,
它们可能没有按我们的计划进行，
but we set them all up.
但我们确实都安排好了。
[static sizzle]
[静电嘶嘶声]
What was that?
那是什么？
Did you set that up too?
你是不是也安排了那个？
No.
没有。
[static sizzling]
[静电嘶嘶声]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
Guys, I'm sure there's an explanation for this.
伙计们，我确信这有解释的。
Don't freak out!
别慌！
Superstitions are real!
迷信是真的！
And...now I broke everyone.
而现在...我把大家都吓坏了。
So, hey, last night did you happen to run
所以，嘿，昨晚你是不是碰巧同时
the dishwasher, vacuum, washer, and dryer
运行了洗碗机、吸尘器、洗衣机和烘干机？
all at the same time?
全开了？
Bingo! The big four.
宾果！四大件。
Well, you blew the big fuse. Everything stopped mid-cycle,
好吧，你把主保险丝烧了。所有设备都中途停了下来，
and now nothing is clean.
现在什么都没洗干净。
You mean it's not "Anne Clean."
你是说不是‘安妮清洁’。
No, I mean it's not any kind of clean.
不，我是说没有任何一种清洁。
Don't step on a crack. Don't step on a crack.
别踩到裂缝。别踩到裂缝。
Don't step on a crack.
别踩到裂缝。
I stepped on a crack!
我踩到裂缝了！
Quick! Spin around to undo the curse!
快！转个圈解除诅咒！
Would you stop that?
你能别这样吗？
[sighs]
[叹气]
- Where's Ricky? - I don't know.
- Ricky在哪儿？ - 我不知道。
Last time I saw him,
上次我看到他时，
he was yelling at the map ball.
他正在对地图球大喊大叫。
You mean...
你是说...
the globe?
地球仪？
Round.
圆的。
Flat.
平的。
I don't know which one of you to believe anymore!
我不知道该相信你们中的哪一个了！
Liars!
骗子！
This has gone too far.
这已经太过分了。
Ricky, superstitions aren't real.
Ricky，迷信不是真的。
We were behind all the things that happened--
我们背后操控了所有发生的事情——
the toothbrush, the shower curtain,
牙刷，浴帘，
the broken doorknob-- all of it.
坏掉的门把手——所有的。
But what about Dicky's chair breaking
但Dicky的椅子坏了，
and Nicky's milk being spoiled?
还有Nicky的牛奶变质了是怎么回事？
Those were supposed to happen to you.
那些本应该是发生在你身上的。
But they didn't.
但它们没有。
Yeah. They happened to us instead.
是的。它们反而发生在我们身上了。
Because of bad luck.
因为运气不好。
It's not bad luck.
这不是运气不好。
Nicky didn't walk under the ladder,
Nicky没有走过梯子下面，
so why would he have bad luck?
所以他为什么会倒霉？
And why has nothing happened to me?
而且为什么什么都没发生在我身上？
Yeah. Why has nothing happened to you?
是的。为什么什么都没发生在你身上？
But whenever we're around you,
但每当我们在你身边时，
bad things happen to us!
坏事就会发生在我们身上！
[Nicky] You made us tempt fate in the first place!
[Nicky] 是你先让我们冒险的！
Yeah!
对！
- Maybe you're the curse! - Yeah!
- 也许你就是那个诅咒！ - 对！
Okay, that's absurd! I'm not the curse.
好吧，这太荒谬了！我不是诅咒。
Bad things don't happen to you just because I'm around!
坏事发生不是因为我在这里！
- Oh... - Uhh!
- 哦... - 呃！
It's the curse!
是诅咒！
How do you explain that we're down here
你怎么解释我们在这下面
and you're up there?
而你却在那上面？
I... [stammers]
我... [结巴]
Tom...
汤姆...
you didn't use furniture polish,
你没有用家具抛光剂，
hard wood wax, and Super Shine
硬木蜡，和超级亮
to clean the floors, did you?
来清洁地板，对吧？
Bingo! The big three.
宾果！三大件。
Honey, you can't do that.
亲爱的，你不能那样做。
It'll make the floors too slippery.
那会让地板太滑。
I mean, I can't explain it,
我是说，我无法解释，
- but there's no way I'm the-- [boys] Oh!
- 但我绝不可能是那个-- [男孩们] 哦！
Oh, my gosh! I am the curse!
哦，我的天哪！我就是那个诅咒！
Our house has gone from bad to worse.
我们的房子已经从糟糕变得更糟了。
So come on, sage, get rid of the curse!
所以快点，鼠尾草，驱除诅咒吧！
Keep your distance.
保持距离。
Don't worry. We will.
别担心。我们会的。
Is that my sage?
那是我的鼠尾草吗？
Yes. I'm using it to get rid of the curse.
是的。我正用它来驱除诅咒。
[doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
[ding-dong]
[叮咚]
Fine. You can get it.
好吧。你去开门。
- Whoa! - Oh!
- 哇！ - 哦！
Just come in!
直接进来吧！
Hey, guys. Happy Friday the 13th!
嘿，伙计们。祝你们黑色星期五快乐！
[thwack]
[啪]
Ow!
哎哟！
So you guys were totally right.
你们完全是对的。
I shouldn't let some silly superstition keep me from having a good time.
我不应该让一些愚蠢的迷信妨碍我享受美好时光。
So I'd love to go with you tonight to see Science Bob.
所以我很想今晚和你们一起去见科学鲍勃。
I'm not going.
我不去。
I don't believe in science anymore.
我不再相信科学了。
I never believed in science.
我从未相信过科学。
You should get out of here, Mae,
你应该离开这里，Mae，
before something bad happens to you.
在不好的事情发生之前。
Don't be crazy, Dawn!
别发疯了，Dawn！
Run, Mae! Save yourself!
快跑，Mae！救你自己！
- Dawn! - Go on, get outta here!
- Dawn！ - 快走，离开这里！
- Get! - But my mom dropped me off-- - I said git!
- 走开！ - 但我妈妈把我送来的—— - 我说了走开！
[doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
[all] I'll get it!
[所有人] 我去开门！
Hello!
你好！
Science Bob?
科学鲍勃？
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
I called him.
我叫他来的。
I'm the one who got you guys freaked out
是我让你们对迷信感到害怕的，
about superstitions, so I asked Science Bob
所以我请科学鲍勃来帮我纠正你们的想法。
to help me set you straight.
孩子们，我想让你们知道，
Kids, I want you to know,
没有什么坏运气或诅咒这种事。
there's no such thing as bad luck or curses.
看，我会向你们证明。
Look, I'll prove it to you.
我会站在Dawn旁边，
I will stand next to Dawn,
你们会看到什么都不会发生。
and you will see that nothing will happen.
你会发现什么都不会发生。
Because, as a celebrated science educator,
因为，作为一名著名的科学教育家，
- I can tell you beyond a-- - Your coat!
- 我可以明确地告诉你—— - 你的外套！
Oh, my gosh, my pen is leaking.
哦，天哪，我的笔漏水了。
That is so weird. I just bought that pen. Huh.
这太奇怪了。我刚买的这支笔。哈。
That's okay-- luckily, I keep a spare coat in my bag.
没关系——幸运的是，我在包里备了一件外套。
[ripping sound]
[撕裂声]
Hopefully, I keep some spare pants in there as well.
希望我也在里面备了些备用裤子。
Ha. Science Bob's spare pants.
哈。科学鲍勃的备用裤子。
Wow. That is so weird.
哇。这真是太奇怪了。
Oh, my gosh. It's you...
哦，我的天哪。是你...
You are cursed!
你被诅咒了！
Bad luck is real!
坏运气是真的！
Yeah! It makes you question everything,
是的！这让你怀疑一切，
like science.
比如科学。
Yeah. I mean, if I was wrong about superstitions,
是的。我是说，如果我对迷信的看法是错的，
what else might I be wrong about?
那我还有什么可能是错的？
Maybe science is all a lie!
也许科学全都是谎言！
But Science Bob,
但是科学鲍勃，
you're Science Bob!
你是科学鲍勃！
Not anymore.
不再是了。
From now on, I'm just Bob.
从现在起，我只是鲍勃。
Or maybe Barista Bob. Bob's got bills.
或者可能是咖啡师鲍勃。鲍勃有账单要付。
Either way, I'm not gonna need this anymore.
无论如何，我不再需要这个了。
[kids gasp]
孩子们惊讶。
Good job, guys.
干得好，伙计们。
You broke Science Bob.
你们把科学鲍勃弄坏了。
Just Bob.
只是鲍勃。
I'll prove to you that science isn't a lie.
我会向你们证明科学不是谎言。
Look, if we mix these two things--
看，如果我们把这两样东西混合——
Stop! You can't mix those.
停！你不能混合那些。
I thought it would make a big, foamy snake thing.
我以为它会变成一个大泡沫蛇。
No...
不...
[glass clinking]
[玻璃碰撞声]
If we want to make a big, foamy snake thing,
如果我们想制造一个大泡沫蛇，
you mix potassium iodide with hydrogen peroxide.
你应该将碘化钾与过氧化氢混合。
Right, Bob?
对吧，Bob？
Whatevs.
随便。
Watch.
看。
Whoa!
哇！
- Cool! - Awesome!
- 酷！ - 太棒了！
Big, foamy snake.
巨大的泡沫蛇。
That will happen
每次混合它们都会这样。
every single time you mix them.
每次你混合它们都会发生。
It's almost like you can depend on it.
几乎就像你可以依赖它一样。
So I guess in this case, science was right.
所以在这个例子中，科学是对的。
I guess.
我想是的。
I wonder what else science has been right about.
我想知道科学还在哪些方面是对的。
Well, there's that cool olive trick Science Bob does.
嗯，还有科学鲍勃做的那个酷橄榄技巧。
Science is always right about that.
科学总是对的。
Exactly!
确实如此！
Every time you add sodium alginate to olive juice
每次你将海藻酸钠加入橄榄汁
and drop it in a calcium chloride solution,
然后滴入氯化钙溶液中，
we know it always does this.
我们都知道它总是会这样。
And we know it will always be good eatin'!
而且我们知道它总是很好吃！
Technically, it's good drinking.
严格来说，是很好喝。
You see, science can prove a lot of things,
你看，科学可以证明很多事情，
so you shouldn't give up on it.
所以你不应该放弃它。
Which means... I probably shouldn't either.
这意味着...我也可能不应该放弃。
I guess there are some things we can know for sure.
我想有些事情我们可以确切地知道。
And some things we can't.
有些事情我们无法知道。
Like... whether this guy's name is Bob or Just Bob.
比如...这个人的名字是Bob还是Just Bob。
And it's actually okay to not have all the answers.
没有所有答案其实也没关系。
Exactly.
没错。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Was this all a setup
这一切是不是都是安排好的
to trick us into feeling better?
为了让我们感觉好一点？
I'll never tell.
我永远不会说。
But I will.
但我会的。
We totally set it up!
我们完全是故意安排的！
Look at this mess!
看看这乱七八糟的！
This has "Tom Clean" written all over it.
这明显是"汤姆搞的鬼"。
Coach is puttin' you in.
教练让你上场。
But wh--what the heck happened here?
但是——这里到底发生了什么？
Science.
科学。
Science Bob?
科学鲍勃？
Are you responsible for this?
这是你干的吗？
Actually...
实际上...
Run!
跑！
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪